We are ONE LOVE ONE HEART
Yes, that's right, this time it's a girl's project!
Yay!
Well, speaking of the middle of February, there is an event that makes girls excited, right?
Don't you know? You know what I mean?
What is it? Ali!
What is it? Andy! What is it?
You're kind of a showoff.
What's that?
No, no, no, no, no! Mr. Andie!
Not Mr. Andy.
Miyu, what is it?
Valentine's Day!
Yay!
That's right! Andy, it's Valentine's Day!
It's Valentine's Day! So, February 14th is Valentine's Day, right? I don't know about you, so I'm going to surprise you with some homemade sweets!
It's Valentine's Day!
What do you think?
Valentine's Day is awesome!
Ichio-san makes a lot of sweets.
You're right.
You've got sweets in there.
Yes, I'm in it.
He's a carpenter... and he's into homemade.
Give him something tasty.
I want you to rethink this.
I'm going to make a present for you today.
I'm going to make you a row of presents today, so let's get to it!
Ohhhh!
I'm making mini chocolate cupcakes!
So cute!
Oh my god, we're all baking together, it's pretty awesome.
Like a girl.
The girls are cooking.
It's the first time in Love One's history.
I'm a good cook.
I've never really succeeded at baking, so I'm a little nervous today.
So I'm a little nervous today.
Do you think you'll be okay?
By the way, I cooked for the summer camp project.
No, we cooked for other people.
And a frying pan.
In the bathtub... and I've been waiting for a while.
How about making sweets?
Sweets are a big problem, aren't they?
I wanted to make it absolutely delicious.
I've been making sweets for a long time.
I've made a lot of mistakes.
So...
Well, I want the boys to eat them.
I want to make them delicious.
The only thing I can make with pancake mix is cupcakes, so I decided to make these cupcakes.
So I decided to make these cupcakes because I want them to taste good, and cupcakes are the only thing you can make with pancake mix.
So that's why I decided to make these.
I hope it will be delicious!
I'm waiting.
I thought it was too heavy.
I see.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I tried pouring it over a cup and oooh ... That's why I'm always making mistakes.
I'm very impatient.
So today, calm down.
Calm down.
I hope I can do it calmly.
Even when I'm making something like this.
Thinking about us
I think about us when I'm making these.
Well...
I think that whatever the result will be
I think.
I see.
Hold this for me.
But you girls have finally gotten into cooking, haven't you?
That's right.
The boys have done better than I expected.
I'm serious.
We were all talking about how they could do it.
That's what we all imagined.
It was even better than we imagined.
I'll just pour the rest in here.
Thank you.
You must be anxious when you're making it.
I know.
I really am.
I don't know if it's going to taste good.
Here you go.
Have a good day.
I hope it doesn't burn.
I'm sure they'll look great when they're all lined up.
Looks so good!
It's done, it's done, it's done!
I'm having fun! It's done, it's done, it's done!
Let's enjoy!
I'm the one who made the melt-in-your-mouth, Honda-style chocolat...
I made a mistake, it's a Honda style muffin. I've been at home for a long time, so I thought I'd start something new, and I've been baking sweets.
I've been making gâteau chocolates, cupcakes, and cakes.
I have made cakes before.
So I was surprised to learn that you can cook. You think you can cook, don't you?
But I might be able to do it.
Please watch.
I'll cut it. It's tender, not like milk.
Look, there's this one that won't open at the last minute.
It's a little bit tricky.
By the way, this is the important part of the melting process.
It melts, doesn't it?
It melts.
This is it.
With love
Pinch of goo
Oh, my gosh!
What a cute ange
Oh, really?
But it looks good.
Yeah, it is.
It's not good, it's not good, it's not good.
Thirty minutes.
Oh, no.
I'd like to make the surface of the muffin dough.
I don't know.
I thought it was me.
I thought I was being a little bit flamboyant, but... wait a minute... aren't you being a little bit flamboyant?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm right behind you, but I'm...
I'm right behind you.
Wait a minute.
100 grams is pretty long, isn't it?
No, seriously, that's a lot of work.
What?
That's a lot of work.
Charts and graphs.
Oh! Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. I've been at 49 all day. That's a lot... a gram. Yeah, I've got a lot.
158 milligrams.
Oh, are you singing?
50 milligrams.
It's like, "What is it?
It's really good. It's too funny.
Yay.
This much?
Oh, that's about right.
Oh, it's so perfect.
Oh, it looks delicious.
I want to eat it.
This is just right.
But not too much. It's so good! I want some! Just the right amount!
But not too much!
You've got it!
It's done!
Here you go.
All of it.
Into the preheated
Into the oven
I'd like to put them in the oven.
Okay. Okay.
Now we're gonna bake it for 25 minutes.
Twenty-five minutes.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
I'm nervous.
It's done.
It's good.
I think I got 100 points.
Yay!
I'll give it one more stab.
You could have painted it.
Oh, but it melts! Look at that.
I made it kind of melt.
Maybe this will work!
Yay!
I want to make orange doughnuts!
Not Valentine's Day chocolate at all.
The recipe is pretty easy to follow.
I chose this one because it's so refreshing and delicious!
I will do my best to make it!
I've been baking cakes for the members since Isshin.
This is the second time I've made a cake for Lou.
I've only cooked with my hands.
I've been trying to improve my girl power lately.
So...
I've been trying to improve my cooking skills.
I've been trying to make cooking a hobby.
I've been working hard on recipes.
I even write recipes on a piece of paper.
It's an orange doughnut.
I write them on a piece of paper.
I write on a piece of paper.
You're very stylish, Mr. Ichi.
Really?
They fly so fast.
You have to smudge it until it turns white.
I'll use it as a decoration.
I'll do it a lot.
I don't like being alone.
I always have my mom next to me.
Mom! Ichi's mom!
She's really great.
She's amazing at baking!
She's a great cook
She can make anything!
Like little waffles.
I really like the ones Ichi's mom makes.
She makes them a lot at Luce's, Mom. Yeah, I just like to keep it light and refreshing.
Is that your mom's recipe? I think it's my mom's recipe.
I'll show you.
Have you ever made chocolate or watermelon by yourself? No.
My mom is a worrier and won't let me be alone because she says you can't do it alone, so this is what happens when you're alone.
I sifted the baking powder and flour like this.
I sifted the baking powder and the flour like this, and that's probably what it is.
You know, there are solids in the flour.
It's not good if there are solids.
Wait a minute! What's wrong with us?
Is the fact that Mom isn't here a failure in itself?
Okay...
What's this?
It smells so good.
I think I gained a gram.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay, I'll leave it alone.
I'm gonna let it sit for a while until it ferments, until it's all mousy.
Okay, now we're going to make the coating.
First of all, 100 grams of flour and powdered sugar
90 grams.
And the juice of an orange. Oh, you have to squeeze this.
This, this, this, what?
Squeeze it first.
Yes, okay.
Oh, I made a mistake! Direction.
What kind of mistake?
But it'll work?
Anything's possible! You just have to narrow it down, right?
I can do it. I can do it.
Come on!
It's gonna be okay.
I mean, it's not too great.
I mean, it's not like it's mussed up or anything.
I'm really nervous.
But I'm sure the boys...
They'll tell you everything's delicious.
They'll put it in.
Fluffy, fluffy, fluffy.
They were all eating chocolate.
Put two in.
No, no, no. No, I'm the same.
No, they're the same.
Look! It's so pretty! Looks so good! Now we just need to decorate it.
Yummy!
I'm going to make a gâturne chocolat.
I'm going to put truffles in it to make it kind of soft.
How many times did you practice?
I practiced 3 times.
That's great! That's great, Yuna!
You're really good!
Yuna, you're really good, you're really good, you're really good, you're really good, you're really good, you're really good, you're really good
You know I can't cook rice and stuff.
Well, I don't have an image of you.
But it's true that I have an image of you being able to cook.
So... so... so...
So we'll have to work a little harder.
I'm afraid we won't be able to provide food anymore.
That's wonderful.
Anything goes, as long as you put it in there.
I'm not looking forward to seeing how they react to that.
I'm not looking forward to it.
Oh, yeah, sure, I might be floating it. I'm sure that's delicious.
Wow, I love it!
Oh, my gosh!
I've never seen anything like this before.
Wow, that's so cool, Nacchan!
Thanks, Nacchan!
I wonder which one it is.
That's nice.
Careful, mix it up, mix it up, mix it up.
I'm gonna mix it up
Oh, my gosh, look at you already.
It's a vortex.
Oh, it looks so good!
It's kind of like that.
What is it?
Bread.
The bread.
Look, marble pancakes.
Looks good.
It looks amazing!
It looks like pound cake!
I don't know what it is, but I've seen something like that before.
That's it!
It's a museum.
What? A museum?
Art gallery, art gallery, art gallery.
Thank you very much. Art museum?
Yes, a museum.
It's cute.
It's a bear.
A bear?
I was going to make truffles.
But I didn't have time.
I'm pretty sure it's in there.
I'm sorry.
I thought it would taste better with truffles.
That's the point.
What's that? What's the point?
The point is to be prepared.
Huh?
Delicious-looking truffles.
If you wrap it up and eat it when it's a little warm, it'll turn into a truffle.
It's a bit like Hondan chocolates.
But it's okay, because this one is just as good.
It's totally fine.
Hot, hot, hot, hot!
Hot, hot, hot.
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
Ready?
Is that two minutes?
10?
12 minutes?
15 minutes.
Fifteen minutes.
Let's get this thing started.
Open!
Wow! It's swelling up. There's a little something to squeeze.
Smells great!
Smells so good!
Oh, man! Yay!
Recipe-wise, I want to make bear cupcakes,
I'm not sure if they'll be bears, but I'm going to make cupcakes anyway!
I'm going to make
Once chiffon
Protein chiffon cake
I made it and it turned out like a rice cracker
and it turned out like a rice cracker.
It was really thick, but it turned out like this, brown.
I made a green matcha and it turned out brown.
I'm not confident
I'm not confident.
I can't do it.
But I'm going to do my best today.
It's so interesting to see Miyu making something.
It's too fresh and super interesting.
What did you say?
I couldn't imagine. Miyu came to wear a lepron.
What? I really didn't get it. Miyu came with an apron and 60 ml.
Oh, no!
Oh, no, no, no!
Are you sure you don't want to have two?
Why do you have two?
Is this okay?
Mew, what are you doing?
What are you doing, Mew?
So that's what you're doing.
So that's how it is.
So that's what it is.
That's how it is.
That's how it is?
Is that what it is?
Is that what you mean or is that what you mean or is that what you mean? Who is this spinning thing to? Oh my God, is this okay? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Oh, I see what you're doing.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's okay.
This is too much fun.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I put in too many of these.
I think it's time...
I think it was this one...
I think I put in eight ass cases, not eight.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
You can stay until the sixth minute.
You good?
Yeah!
It's too shallow.
Miyu.
It's good.
Oh, I could drink it!
At first I was going to use something like oo-daifuku (rice cake with sweetened bean curd), but
But then I thought, "Valentine's Day is all about chocolate," so I decided to go with chocolate.
As a result, it was a little cute and I chose it on a hunch, love at first sight!
I'm sure you're looking forward to it!
But what should I do?
Which one is it?
I'm really looking forward to it, but what should I do?
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'd like to say I'm looking forward to it after I've made something tasty and reassuring!
10,000 yen pack of cake cups!
Here we go!
It's so cute!
With love, with love
I'd like to go on with my love to all the Rasmeemans!
We've been learning about food loss in school for a long time, so food loss is forbidden.
Everyone has no food loss?
Yes, Myu-chan is trying to eliminate food loss today.
I had a meat bun for lunch and Myu and I wanted to have a meat bun for lunch to eliminate doloshes!
Yuna and I had burgers together.
Yuna said she really wanted to go, so I went with her.
Then we both thought about the food rosh...
Myu-chan said "I have to buy one too!
So we did!
It was really good!
We were so happy!
It looks delicious, so I'd like to try it.
Is it possible to put chocolate in it? Oh well.
I'm going to put these truffles in the dribs and drabs.
Wow, that's amazing. That's genius.
I bet it's delicious.
It's definitely delicious.
Ina-chan, do you want a bite?
Chocolate.
Cheers!
Yum!
That means he's already confessed his feelings for you.
That's right! Chocolates of love.
Yes!
Oh, they're so cute!
Aren't they cute? I bought them because I fell in love at first sight.
Okay, please, please, please!
May they burn!
Am I right? I hope they bake! Is that right? This one.
OK!
It's done!
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
It's hot!
Really hot!
Can you cook it?
Can't it?
Maybe it's a bar of chocolate?
That's what I'm talking about! Oh, the end of the year? No, I don't think so. Maybe that's it. Chocolate bars? Huh! That's what I'm talking about! Oh, am I there?
It smells so good.
Cute.
Kanna.
It's too chocolate.
I can tell.
Is everyone okay?
I'm sorry, I'm just...
ED.